Sergei Chunarev

+49 15235849119 · chunarev.se.a.g@gmail.com

Location: Munich, Germany LinkedIn: <u>sergei-chunarev</u> Github: <u>chunarevsa</u>



JAVA AND KOTLIN SOFTWARE ENGINEER

My extensive experience includes working for one of the three largest internet providers in my country, for a middle company that worked with big factories and in a high-growth startup. I've taken part in the development process and mostly worked with the backend.

KEY COMPETENCIES

Java, Kotlin, Spring Framework, Spring Boot, Spring Data, Spring Security, Gradle, Maven, Tomcat, Hibernate, Postgre-SQL, Docker, Microservices, RabbitMQ, Kafka, Mockito, Grafana, React, TypeScript, JavaScript, TDD, Git, Jira, Confluence.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

CashFlow, May 2023 - Present

Java and Kotlin Developer

- actively participated in Event Storming and contributed to the development of application architecture.
- proactively studied and implemented new development technologies and methodologies.
- communicated with focus groups and made adjustments accordingly.
- developed 2 microservices from 0 to MVP.

RTK Information Technology, Feb 2022 - May 2023

Java and Kotlin Developer

- developed and maintained the server side of personal account of RTK IT subscribers
- initiated optimization of legacy code segments, rewriting them in Kotlin.
- doubled the completion rate of code reviews by developing a service that timely notifies developers about pending reviews with integration of Upsource via Discord. Successfully propagated this service to neighboring departments.
- had high evaluations according to the polls from different departments that I worked with (4,6 / 5)

KTR Engineering, Apr 2020 - Feb 2022

Java Software Developer

- developed a service providing access to construction documentation, information about consumables and their expiration dates.
- quickly integrated into the team and workflow.
- actively sought and applied knowledge learnt from colleagues, participating in educational programs.
- provided prompt technical support to users, resolving issues and inquiries related to service functionality and usage.
- achieved high task completion rates per release.

EDUCATION

Engineer, Bachelor's degree

Majors: Chemical Engineering

Department Equipment of the Oil and Gas Industry Perm National Research Polytechnic University

ADDITIONAL

Languages: English (B2), German (A2),

Russian (Native)

Preffered place of work: Munich or remotely

Work permition: Yes (National)